you know my real issue with they go low we go high is they've always been low
we don't have to go high we're already on a higher vibration that assumes that we are
starting on an equal plane no we not michelle no we not y'all are on an equal plane with them
people because y'all are playing with them people y'all are having dinner with them people y'all
are sharing hard candies with them people some of us ain't on no equal plane with them people
we couldn't the lowest we could ever go would not even achieve the height that they could ever reach
i need y'all to understand this you preventing folks from pulling you into the depths
of their sadism is not you going low that's you preventing them from pulling you from the heights
of your high vibration so no ain't no they go low we go high it's get off me okay
but i'm bum he began to support the labor unions uh he questioned government allocation of resources
he advocated for reparations where are we cutting the check it was after all of this when he had
evolved into martin luther the king that this nation thought to be rid of him